Now it started,
so we have to we can remove parky and
How hard?
other things.
The other thing is sexual understanding,
whether Victor is needed or not.
Okay.
This, what is it?
Bhagat as killer.
So the idea is actually if it is Victor
DB,
we could expose the database as a tool to
the agent which can use this as actually
like a baseline.
Actual entry, right?
It can store both.
What?
So basically the SQLite FTS file versus
actual vector DB,
the dedicated vector DB you are talking
about, right?
Yeah,
dedicated vector DBi believe actually
SQLite itself supports something new
nowadays.
We just actually check for that SQLite
vectors.
Escalate on the Internet itself.
Yeah, search for escalate director.
They have something on escalate whack.
A brute force and zero preprocessing
preindexing required operates Daribian
standard blog columns.
I think this is not actually like a this
one.
This is not actually like a group shows.
What is it?
This is the Sqlide Wax 6 ecosystem
operates similar to Sqlide's full text
search extension,
it acts as a embedded virtual table
engine.
Okay, we will go text something for now,
let us get things working,
and then if needed, we will stop escalate.
Yeah.
Okay,
and the implementation has to be done in
4 steps, I believe,
as we were discussing in the afternoon.
Just asking you to explode.
What's?
So like the tool should be implemented in
steps.
The first step is actually asking you to
explorer an app and report its ending.
And then actually recording the actions.
We actually like you talked about the
sequence, am I right?
If we can come up with a sequence and
actually reptile events,
we can actually decide on like whether or
not to finish.
Anything else?
OK, so wait a second.
Can you repeat last thing I didn't get?
Big what?
No, it was good.
You said you were talking about the 4
steps.
So I ask you to split,
split the overall thing into from 4
sections and pick it up them,
pick them one by one.
The first thing is asking me to, yeah,
the first thing is to like ask it to just
The implementation.
actually explore,
capture the actions and the evidence.
Mhm.
Okay,
the second thing is to look identifying
bugs.
The 3rd thing is aligning with the user.
The 4th thing is actually repopulating
the knowledge base.
The first thing is actually wiring the
knowledge base with this one once again.
The test journal that completes us.
Right.
Okay,
so the like the implementation itself
should be made into these steps, okay.
In steps.
Okay, I'll do that.
so the idea is actually if even actually
one step actually,
the idea is actually spend some 4 hours
per step.
If actually something proves costly,
then we'll revisit whether or not to do
this.
Mhm.
Okay, anything else?
But I know I'll get the transcript and
update the doc. so.
Okay, see you ma'am. Bye.
Welcome.